A Guide to the Rich Family Papers, 1798-1952
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
Rich Family Papers 1798-1952
Special Collections, Kegley Library
1994.1
128 folders.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Mary B. Kegley in 1994.
Custodial History
These papers were purchased in the 1970s by Mary B. Kegley and Dr. W. R. Chitwood at an estate sale. At the death of Dr. Chitwood in 1993, his widow, Ruth Ann Chitwood, gave her husband's share of the papers to Mary B. Kegley.
Biographical Information
A prosperous furniture empire was born in 1830 when Fleming Kean Rich and Thomas Moyer united their talents as cabinet makers and businessmen. In the late 1820s, Fleming Rich moved to Wytheville, married Ann Catherine Moyers, and worked in his father-in-law's cabinetmaking shop.
The firm of Moyers and Rich expanded their trade to include manufacture of pie safes, beds, wardrobes, sofas, signboards, and coffins. Repair of fine furniture and musical instruments as well as a delivery service offering transportation throughout southwest Virginia also enable Moyers and Rich to prosper. Fleming Rich, a shrewd merchant, offered funeral services to complement his fine coffins.
With the death of Thomas Moyers in 1840, Rich renamed the firm Fleming K. Rich Furniture Shop. His brother Nimrod Rich assisted with tinsmithing while numerous apprentice cabinet and furniture makers created distinctive pieces of fine furniture sold throughout the region.
Ann Catherine Moyers and Fleming Rich had five children, of whom one, William W. Rich, survived childhood. Catherine Rich died in 1836 and Fleming Rich remarried in 1839. His second wife, Mary Thompson Johnson, was nicknamed Polly or Molly T. Together, they had six children, two of whom died in infancy.
When Fleming Rich died in 1861, his son William W. Rich assumed control of the family business. His sons, William Rich and George Rich, continued the tradition of fine furniture manufacture and sale until 1943. By 1871, William Rich had turned his Main Street store in Wytheville into a fashionable furniture gallery while his workers built furniture in a water-powered plant on Union Street (present day Withers Road.)
David Allen Rich, son of Fleming Rich and Mary Polly Thompson Rich, married Mary Margaret Allen in 1881. He served as deputy sheriff, superintendent of the water works, and clerk for the town of Wytheville. His daughter, Mary Rich, married P. A. Early in 1908. His son Fleming Rich married May Hamilton while his son Robert Rich married Anna Gleaves.
Mary Polly Thompson Rich operated a boarding house in Wytheville until her death in 1891. A tourist guide of 1887 claimed that Rich's Boarding House had been a popular boarding house of summer visitors for 15 years.
Scope and Content
Arranged into seven series, the Rich Family Papers concentrate upon the business activities of Fleming Kean Rich and his family including furniture and coffin design, transportation, and boarding house operation.
Series I includes correspondence arranged chronologically and dating from 1832 to 1952, of Fleming Kean Rich, his second Mary Polly Thompson Rich, his son David Allen Rich, and numerous customers, business colleagues and relations. Highlighting the collection are thirty-five letters from Wythe Countians and others requesting Fleming Rich to build coffins. Of additional significant interest are the many letters to Rich and his father-in-law, Thomas Moyers, ordering furniture including pie safes, beds, and wardrobes. The diversity of economic status and residence of these customers emphasizes the popularity of Fleming Rich as a cabinet and furniture maker in Southwest Virginia.
The business and family correspondence of Mary Polly Thompson Johnson Rich and her father, Palser Johnson, is also found in Series I. Mary Rich operated a boarding house in Wytheville from the 1860s to the early 1890s.
Bills and receipts dating from 1798 to 1937 from the business ventures of Thomas Moyers, Fleming Rich, Mary Rich, and Palser Johnson comprise much of the financial records in Series II. Bills and receipts of Fleming Kean Rich are arranged in two sections; one chronological and one alphabetical by individual business or trade. This particular arrangement scheme follows the original provenance arrangement.
Of primary interest in Series III, legal records, are four contracts between Fleming Kean Rich and Thomas Moyers and apprentices dating from 1827 to 1860. Summons, indentures, receipts, and inventory of the estate and insurance policies of Mary Polly Thompson Rich are also found in this series.
Series IV contains land records including deeds dating from 1810 to 1889 and plats and surveys.
Genealogical records compiled by Mary Rich Early, daughter of David Allen Rich, her husband P. A. Early, her son P. A. Early Jr., and historian Mary B. Kegley comprise Series V. Families covered in this series include Allen family, Johnson family, Rich family, Rosenheim family, and the Williams family. Much of the Rich family genealogical notes concerns medieval and Tudor-Stuart era British lineage.
With Series VI, books, the focus reverts to the business of Thomas Moyers and Fleming Rich. Account books (1829-1858) and ledgers (1832-1887) document daily transactions of a prominent furniture making trade.
Series VII, miscellaneous records (1834-1891), includes school reports, recipes for various foods, varnishes and stains, militia fines of Fleming Rich, and application for business licenses by Mary Rich.
Photocopies (1838-1860) of Rich papers owned by a private individual form Series VIII. Included are four letters from John Rich of Benton County, Arkansas to his brother Fleming Kean Rich. Receipts and tax records of Palser Johnson complete this series.
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence. 1832-1952, Undated., 29 folders
  - Folder 1. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1832-1839., 7 items. (Series-folder 1:1)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich and Thomas Moyers from Peter Gose of Burkes Garden, Randal McGavock, Joseph Cooley, William Barringer, C. H. Griffith of Baltimore, Maryland, Currie [unknown] of Louisa, Kentucky, and William Dills of Tazewell.
  - Folder 2. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1840., 7 items. (Series-folder 1:2)
    This folder contains letters to Thomas Moyers and Fleming Kean Rich from G. V. Goble of Louisa, Kentucky, Randal D. Seales of Madison, North Carolina, Joseph Meridith of Blountville, Tennessee, B. G. Simpson of Rogersville, Tennessee, and Thomas Eagleson of New Carlisle, Ohio.
  - Folder 3. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1841., 14 items. (Series-folder 1:3)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from Joseph Graham, Peter Litz of Burkes Garden, Virginia, George W. Moyers of Buffalo Hide, Tennessee, David Gose of Burkes Garden, Virginia, G. V. Goble of Louisa, Kentucky, R. A. French of Giles County, Virginia, Z. L. Sprinkle of Marion, Virginia, N. H. Lee of Barbourville, Kentucky, Edmund Wills of Newbern, Virginia, David Giester of Jonesborough, Tennessee, and Henry Earhart of Black Lick, Wythe County, Virginia.
  - Folder 4. Fleming Kean Rich. 1842, 14 items. (Series-folder 1:4)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from William Milnon of Saltville, Virginia, Thomas Sanders, Reuben Shavits of Athens, Tennessee, Amos Spear of Lynchburg, Virginia, Hugh White of Lynchburg, Virginia, W. T. Nicholls of Louisa, Kentucky, David Graham, Thomas Early of Pulaski, Virginia, Samuel Snider and George Snider of Burkes Garden, Virginia, J. G. Cecil of Pulaski, Virginia, George W. Moyers of Buffalo Hide, Tennessee, J. E. Brown, and H. B. Hall.
  - Folder 5. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1843., 7 items. (Series-folder 1:5)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from H. V. Hance of Newbern, Virginia, P. L. Woolwine of Newbern, Virginia, G. W. Sprinkle and S. D. Sprinkle of Marion, Virginia, Thomas Wood, George W. Hines, and Israel [unknown].
  - Folder 6. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1844., 13 items. (Series-folder 1:6)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from Hugh White of Abingdon, Virginia, David Graham of Jackson Forge, Virginia, G. W. Hines, James Graham, P. L. Woolwine of Newbern, Virginia, A. T. Newberry, L. F. Dawson, P. B. Sanders, William E. Sprinkle of Marion, Virginia, Peter Litz of Burkes Garden, Virginia, A. Chaffin, John W. Riley of Pulaski County, Virginia, and David Giester of Blountville, Tennessee.
  - Folder 7. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1845., 13 items. (Series-folder 1:7)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from A. B. Durnill of Hillsville, Virginia, James Graham of Drapers Valley, Virginia, A. Gregory of Austinville, Virginia, John Lawder of Burkes Garden, Virginia, William Wilkinson, A. S. Kincannon of Seven Mile Ford, Virginia, J. L. Chandler, Agnes L. McGavock, Thomas Sanders, and G. W. Hines of Hillsville, Virginia.
  - Folder 8. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1846., 8 items. (Series-folder 1:8)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from Ed W. Lockett of Cripple Creek Forge, Virginia, James O. Busny, W. W. Hanson of Seven Mile Ford, Virginia, Agnes L. McGavock of Cedar Hill, Virginia, and William L. Thornton of Hillsville, Virginia.
  - Folder 9. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1847., 21 items. (Series-folder 1:9)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from A. Gregory, David M. Cloyd of Newbern, Virginia. E. W. Lockett, W. W. Heuser of Seven Mile Ford, Virginia, Edward Fox of St. Mary's Catholic Church, Wytheville, Virginia, L. W. Crouet of Philadelphia, Tennessee, Robert Holliday of Cripple Creek, Virginia, Jonathan R. Richardson of Cedar Hill, Virginia, W. W. Hanson of Seven Mile Ford, Virginia, G. W. Reines of Red Bluff, Virginia, Robert Highley, F. K. Munsey of Washington, Tennessee, John Sanders of Jacksons Ferry, Virginia, Jacob Spraeker, J. E. Brown, John Williams, and P. Addison of Cedarville, Virginia.
  - Folder 10. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1848., 10 items. (Series-folder 1:10)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from Lynch A. Currin of Pulaski County, Virginia, William Vaughn of Grayson County, Virginia, D. Flemming of Kingston, Tennessee, T. K. Munsey and Mary J. Munsey of Decatur, Tennessee, William P. Kirkbride of Austinville, Virginia, W. M. Chatwill, Robert B. Highley, M. K. Callaway, and J. T. Currin of Seven Mile Ford, Virginia.
  - Folder 11. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1849., 11 items. (Series-folder 1:11)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from William Chatwill of Newbern, Virginia, P. Anderson of New Market, Virginia, Robert Roper, J. Pryse of Fort Chiswell, Virginia, William F. Gardner of Canton, Virginia, Robert B. Highley, J. H. Howe, and David N. Sears of Abingdon, Virginia.
  - Folder 12. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1850-1852., 19 items. (Series-folder 1:12)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from A. S. Kincannon of Seven Mile Ford, Virginia, William E. Moore of Newbern, Virginia, J. W. Pryse of Fort Chiswell, Virginia, Martin Brown of Grayson County, Virginia, E. T. Taylor, G. A. Catron of Dublin, Virginia, John S. Earheart, David Graham, Robert P. Williams, Jacob Harsh of Spencer, Indiana, Henry S. Bowen of Tazewell County, Virginia, Thomas M. Rider of Giles Court House, Virginia, John W. Vaughn of Carroll County, Virginia, and Robert Sayers.
  - Folder 13. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1853., 11 items. (Series-folder 1:13)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from James Mahood Jr. of Burkes Garden, Virginia, R. W. Nowlin of Wytheville, Virginia, George A. Catron of Newbern, Virginia, P. Anderson of Newbern, Virginia, Thomas Wood of Drapers Valley, Virginia, W. F. Hurst of Carroll County, Virginia, and Robert Sayers.
  - Folder 14. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1854., 13 items. (Series-folder 1:14)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from Jones & Potts Company of Richmond, Virginia, H. F. Heuser of Carroll County, Virginia, J. W. Scott, John W. Moore, Thomas Taylor of Rural Retreat, Virginia, Mathew Fitzgerald, David Sexton, George A. Catron of Newbern, Virginia, J. K. Johnson, R. N. Sanders, George Hudson, and John Wilkinson of Hillsville, Virginia.
  - Folder 15. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1855., 13 items. (Series-folder 1:15)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from Jacob Miller, A. J. Graham, Jessee Peery of Burkes Garden, Virginia, A. F. Gregory of Wythe Union Lead Mines Company, Austinville, Virginia, George A. Catron of Newbern, Virginia, J. W. Rodgers of Newbern, Virginia, H. Gleaves, Williams Sayers, S. N. Sayers, Laura Miller of Poplar Camp, Virginia, and John Morrison of Rosedale, Russell County, Virginia.
  - Folder 16. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1856., 7 items. (Series-folder 1:16)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from George A. Catron of Newbern, Virginia, John Jones of Burkes Garden, Virginia, Robert H. Ward, and James Hart sell of Gladesboro, Virginia.
  - Folder 17. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1857., 14 items. (Series-folder 1:17)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from George A. Catron of Newbern, Virginia, John Allison, Susie Perkins of Elk Creek, Virginia, A. J. Nye of Mechanicsburg, Virginia, Philip Anderson of Newbern, Virginia, George Stuart of Wytheville, Virginia. A. F. Gregory of Wythe Union Lead Mine Company, Austinville, Virginia, Alexander Peirce, Samuel Smithson of Salem, Virginia, James Oglesby Davidson of Henry Court House, Virginia, Thomas J. Moyers of Jeffersonville, Virginia, and John D. Morrison.
  - Folder 18. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1858-1859., 15 items. (Series-folder 1:18)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from George A. Catron of Newbern, Virginia, M. F. Floyd, Houghton & Brothers Company of New York, New York, A. Sanders, J. H. Cochran of Kents Mill, Virginia, George F. O. Trigg, M. McCormack of Lynchburg, Virginia, Thomas M. Rider of Giles Court House, Virginia, and John Maddon.
  - Folder 19. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. 1860., 3 items. (Series-folder 1:19)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from George A. Catron of Newbern, Virginia and George W. Moyers of Tampico, Tennessee.
  - Folder 20. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich. Undated., 23 items. (Series-folder 1:20)
    This folder contains letters to Fleming Kean Rich from E. W. Lockett, Red Bluff, Virginia, John Lowder of Burkes Garden, Virginia, Stephen McGavock, Elizabeth Perman, F. P. Brown, George A. Catron, John Steenancer, John Williams, M. T. Stuart, James Pearman, Charles C. Tate, Alexander Pierce, James Gibboney, James E. Robertson, E. E. Crockett, John Gannaway, S. Sayers, G. A. Taliaferro, Alexander S. Mathews, John Wilkinson, N. H. Crockett, and Charles Tate.
  - Folder 21. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich - Coffin Orders. 1844-1853., 11 items. (Series-folder 1:21)
    This folder contains orders to Fleming Kean Rich for coffins from Gordon C. Kent, Mary B. Fleming, Adam Sanders, Legrand Sexton of Reed Island, Virginia, Hugh Spence of Black Lick, Wythe County, Virginia, D. B. Sanders, W. Alexander Stuart at Hillsville, Virginia, John Earhart, and James H. Lee Nucholls of Red Bluff, Virginia.
  - Folder 22. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich - Coffin Orders. 1854-1859., 15 items. (Series-folder 1:22)
    This folder contains orders to Fleming Kean Rich for coffins from Steel and Deaton Company, William F. Kincannon, C. Grayson of Graysons Mills, Virginia, E. Ward, William Sayers, D. B. Sanders, Jacob Haller, J. K. Johnson, Isaac Hudson, John Melton Howard, Peter Butner, A. D. Gage, William Sayers, and R. J. Haller.
  - Folder 23. Correspondence - Fleming Kean Rich - Coffin Orders. Undated., 9 items. (Series-folder 1:23)
    This folder contains orders to Fleming Kean Rich for coffins from J. W. Scott, William H. Brown, Stephen McGavock, C. L. Crockett, R. Crockett, G. S. Crockett, and notes by Mary B. Kegley on coffin orders.
  - Folder 24. Correspondence - Mary Polly Thompson Rich. 1862-1879., 10 items. (Series-folder 1:24)
    This folder contains letters to Mary Polly Thompson Rich from George A. Catron of Dublin, Virginia, J. W. Dicky of Clear Branch, Washington County, Virginia, Jonathan Halliday of Lynchburg, Virginia, John Fletcher Rich of Colusa, California, United States Department of Agriculture, John W. Paulett of Knoxville, Tennessee, E. Solomon of New Orleans, Louisiana, and E. H. Fowles of Mobile, Alabama.
  - Folder 25. Correspondence - Mary Polly Thompson Rich. 1881-1890, Undated., 12 items. (Series-folder 1:25)
    This folder contains letters to Mary Polly Thompson Rich from N. Q. Allen of Washington, Tennessee, George F. [illegible] of Wytheville, Virginia, Sally B. Hammer of Richmond Female Institute, Richmond, Virginia, George C. Phelps of Columbus, Georgia, Sarah Johnson of Lansdowne, Pennsylvania, J. Robert Rich, John Fletcher Rich of Colusa, California, Lena Lawson of Wytheville, Virginia, B. A. Macon of Charlottesville, Virginia, and Mary N. Hurt.
  - Folder 26. Correspondence - David Allen Rich. 1872-1912., 12 items. (Series-folder 1:26)
    This folder contains letters to David Allen Rich from Letitia Rich Martin of Morganfield, Kentucky, John Fletcher Rich of Colusa, California, Robert Harvey Allen of Birmingham, Alabama, Thomas S. Drury of Wytheville, Virginia, May Hamilton Rich of Beaver Creek, North Carolina, Robert Rich of Waiterville, West Virginia, Willie Hurt of Roanoke, Virginia, Robert Rich of Bandy, Virginia, and Mrs. Early of Abingdon, Virginia.
  - Folder 27. Correspondence - David Allen Rich. 1914, Undated., 11 items. (Series-folder 1:27)
    This folder contains letters to David Allen Rich from Mary Stuart Hurt of Roanoke, Virginia, May Hamilton Rich, Fleming Rich of Beaver Creek, North Carolina, John Fletcher Rich of Colusa, California, and Mary Rich Early.
  - Folder 28. Correspondence - Miscellaneous. 1837-1885., 12 items. (Series-folder 1:28)
    This folder contains miscellaneous correspondence to and from Daniel Hoofnagle, Doran Kinnser & Company, James St. Clair, David White, Thomas Richey, Mary Jane Munsey, Elmira Rich, Moses Lacy, John Fletch Rich, Letitia Rich Morton, Patrick Hagan, H. R. Pettitt, J. P. Johnson, G. J. Holbrook, and G. S. Johnson.
  - Folder 29. Correspondence - Miscellaneous. 1886-1952, Undated., 18 items. (Series-folder 1:29)
    This folder contains miscellaneous correspondence to and from G. S. Johnson, G. J. Holbrook, M. M. Rich, Edward Allen Jr., Holbrook and Thomas, Attorneys, E. H. Umberger, David Allen Rich, Mary Rich, Libbie Allen, George Wood, Rich Brothers Furniture Shop, Edith MacBrine Scotty, Anna Gleaves Rich, Harry Clemons, P. A. Early Jr., John S. Murray, P. A. Early, and Mary Early Rich.
- Series II. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1811-1937, Undated., 63 folders.
  - Folder 1. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1811, 1820s., 19 items. (Series-folder 2:1)
  - Folder 2. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1830-1835., 63 items. (Series-folder 2:2)
  - Folder 3. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1836-1839., 81 items. (Series-folder 2:3)
  - Folder 4. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1840-1841., 70 items. (Series-folder 2:4)
  - Folder 5. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1842-1843., 44 items. (Series-folder 2:5)
  - Folder 6. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1844-1846., 54 items. (Series-folder 2:6)
  - Folder 7. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1847-1849., 42 items. (Series-folder 2:7)
  - Folder 8. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1850-1853., 59 items. (Series-folder 2:8)
  - Folder 9. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1854-1856, 49 items. (Series-folder 2:9)
  - Folder 10. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1857-1859., 31 items. (Series-folder 2:10)
  - Folder 11. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1860s, 14 items. (Series-folder 2:11)
  - Folder 12. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. 1870-1880s, 1913, 1937., 12 items. (Series-folder 2:12)
  - Folder 13. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. Undated., 52 items. (Series-folder 2:13)
  - Folder 14. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts. Undated., 43 items. (Series-folder 2:14)
  - Folder 15. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Dennison Baldwin & Company. 1830-1835., 11 items. (Series-folder 2:15)
  - Folder 16. Financial Records - Blacksmiths. 1833-1869., 14 items (Series-folder 2:16)
  - Folder 17. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Butter & Eggs. 1840-1859, Undated., 18 items. (Series-folder 2:17)
  - Folder 18. Financial Records - Bills & Receipts - Boyd Brothers. 1840-1844., 10 items. (Series-folder 2:18)
  - Folder 19. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Cattle Drovers. 1831-1842, Undated., 5 items. (Series-folder 2:19)
  - Folder 20. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Coffins. 1827-1850., 6 items. (Series-folder 2:20)
  - Folder 21. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Furniture. 1831-1855., 15 items. (Series-folder 2:21)
  - Folder 22. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - William Gibboney and Company. 1833-1844., 38 items. (Series-folder 2:22)
  - Folder 23. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - William Gibboney and Company. 1845-1879, Undated., 31 items. (Series-folder 2:23)
  - Folder 24. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Gabriel Guggenheimer. 1848-1860, Undated., 17 items. (Series-folder 2:24)
  - Folder 25. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Hatters. 1831-1849, Undated., 6 items. (Series-folder 2:25)
  - Folder 26. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Augustus Heuser. 1853-1873., 9 items. (Series-folder 2:26)
  - Folder 27. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Iron. 1832-1846., 57 items. (Series-folder 2:27)
  - Folder 28. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Iron. 1847-1869., 62 items. (Series-folder 2:28)
  - Folder 29. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - James K. Johnson. 1839-1860., 7 items. (Series-folder 2:29)
  - Folder 30. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Kent's Store. 1835-1853, Undated., 26 items. (Series-folder 2:30)
  - Folder 31. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Ephraim McGavock. 1834-1856, Undated., 38 items. (Series-folder 2:31)
  - Folder 32. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Thomas Moyers Estate. 1826-1849, Undated., 45 items. (Series-folder 2:32)
  - Folder 33. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Andrew Jackson Neighbors. 1845-1867, Undated., 7 items. (Series-folder 2:33)
  - Folder 34. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Clayron J. Noel. 1850-1855., 4 items. (Series-folder 2:34)
  - Folder 35. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Jacob Miller, Saddler. 1839-1843., 3 items. (Series-folder 2:35)
  - Folder 36. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Physicians. 1827-1890, Undated., 42 items. (Series-folder 2:36)
  - Folder 37. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Hezekiah Rosenbaum. 1852-1857., 7 items. (Series-folder 2:37)
  - Folder 28. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - James St. Clair. 1830-1839., 34 items. (Series-folder 2:38)
  - Folder 39. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - James St. Clair. 1840-1857, Undated., 44 items. (Series-folder 2:39)
  - Folder 40. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Schools. 1840-1860, Undated., 25 items. (Series-folder 2:40)
  - Folder 41. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Shoes. 1831-1860, Undated., 51 items. (Series-folder 2:41)
  - Folder 42. Financial Records - Bills and Receipts - Thomas H. Simmerman. 1842-1859., 6 items. (Series-folder 2:42)